dailyhealthalerts.com 2019-06-17

# 

                                     PRIVACY POLICY
Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on the Internet as
enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the Internet's vast array of
information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence.
Our Company "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" has created this Privacy Policy to
demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes
how our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" collects information from all
end users of our Internet services (the "Services")-those who access some of our Services
but do not have accounts ("Visitors") as well as those who may purchase Products and/or
pay a monthly service fee to subscribe to the Service ("Members")-what we do with the
information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Members have concerning the
collection and use of such information. We request that you read this Privacy Policy
carefully. By visiting our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" Web site, you
are consenting to our policy of collecting and using your data.
Personal Information Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" Collects
and How It Is Used
Introduction. Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" collects information in
different ways from Visitors and Members who access the various parts of our Services
and the network of Web sites accessible through our Service.
Registration: Members may be asked to provide certain personal information when they
sign up for our Products or Services including name, address, telephone number, billing
information (such as a credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used
to access the Services. The personal information collected from Members during the
registration process is used to manage each Member's account (such as for billing
purposes). This information may be shared with third parties, as stated herein, or in
special circumstances.
 However, in instances where our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" and a
partner jointly promote our Services, we may provide the partner certain personal
information, such as the name, address, and username of persons who subscribed to the
Services as a result of the joint promotion for the purpose of offering you other products
and services.
We may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information
Members provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of
Members). As explained in more detail below, we may use this aggregated and non-
identifying information to sell advertisements that appear on the Services.
Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" collects personal information
through forms you complete on the site, as well as but not limited to contests,
sweepstakes, text messages, e-mails, faxes, telephone calls, postal mail or other

communications with the user, as well as from outside sources such as credit card
processors and database vendors.
For example, when you fill out a form subscribing to our emails, we are sent data
information from our autoresponder company such as your name, email, the website you
signed up from, geographical data such as your city, state, Postal code, country, Latitude,
Longitude, Timestamp, Subscription method and IP address.
Also, with purchases, we supply our member's contact information, to our business
partners, who then may contact the member by telephone after the member purchase.
Sales proceeds are collected by the that business partner company. We also may supply
other companies with contact information, for mail offers we believe would be of interest
to our members, with or without compensation from those companies. At times we may
send an advertisement for a third party product, where we collect the sales proceeds, and
forward the purchaser's information to that third party.
Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" Partners and Sponsors: Some
products and services may be offered to Visitors and Members in conjunction with an
affiliate, independent contractor seller or non-affiliated partner. To provide Visitors and
Members some of these products and services, the partner may need to collect and
maintain personal information.
Online Shopping: At some Web sites, you can purchase products and services or register
to receive materials, such as a newsletter, catalog or new product and service updates. In
many cases, you may be asked to provide contact information, such as your name,
address, email address, phone number, and credit/debit card information.
If you complete an order for someone else, such as an online gift order sent directly to a
recipient, you may be asked to provide information about the recipient, such as the
recipient's name, address, and phone number. Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional
Systems, LLC" has no control over the third parties' use of any personal information you
provide when placing such an order. Please exercise care when doing so.
If you order services or products directly from our Company, "Ringold Nutritional
Systems, LLC", we use the personal information you provide to process that order. We
do share this information with outside parties that we do business with.
Online Advertisements: Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" may display
our online advertisements. In those cases we share information about our Visitors and
Members collected through the registration process as well as through online surveys and
promotions with these advertisers.
Additionally, in some instances, we use this information to deliver tailored
advertisements or joint ventures. For instance, an advertiser or joint venture company
tells us the audience they want to reach and provides us an advertisement tailored to the
audience. Based upon the information we have collected, we may then display or send the

advertisement to the intended audience. Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems,
LLC" does share personal information about its Visitors or Members with these
advertisers or joint venture companies.
By visiting our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" Web site, you are
consenting to our policy of collecting and using your data. If you do not want to consent
to our policy of collecting and using your data you can “opt out” of our Social Network
and Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads advertising policy by notifying
Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" in the following manner:
Social Network and Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads (WCA):
A Custom Audience on Facebook.com is a list of people our Company, "Ringold
Nutritional Systems, LLC" would like to show our ads to on Facebook.com, who have
shown interest in our products and services, with ads we believe would be of interest to
them. This audience consists of people, whose information and email addresses our
Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" already has, because they have already
subscribed to receiving Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" emails.
If you no longer have an interest in our products and services, you can opt-out of seeing
our Company's, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC"'s Facebook.com Website Custom
Audience Ads. Unsubscribing from our Company's, "Ringold Nutritional Systems,
LLC"'s email list will remove you from Company's, "Ringold Nutritional Systems,
LLC"'s internal email database list and stop future emails from our Company, "Ringold
Nutritional Systems, LLC", but not from being shown Facebook.com Website Custom
Audience Ads. The Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads external database, is
different from our Company's, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC"'s internal database
and requires the following Opting-out request.
Opting-out of Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads:
To opt out of our Company's, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC"'s Facebook.com
Custom Audience Ads, send an email, from the email address you are opting out, to
Company's, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" email address
optout@ringoldnutritional.com . Put "Opting Out of Facebook.com Website Custom
Audience Ads " in the subject line of the email. In the body of the email include your
name and email address. Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" staff will
forward your name and email address to Facebook.com with a request to delete you from
all of Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC"'s Facebook.com Website Custom
Audience Ads.
Complete Opt-out From All Communications From "Ringold Nutritional Systems,
LLC"
You can opt-out off all communications from our company, "Ringold Nutritional
Systems, LLC" by notifying us, by using one of the following three methods:

Email us at "optout@ringoldnutritional.com" with "Opt-out of receiving emails from
Ringold Nutritional Systems" in the subject line and include a brief description along side
the email needing to be removed from our mailing list. You may also contact us by phone
at 248-397-4101 and request to be removed from our mailing list. You can also send a
letter to our physical address "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC - 200 W 2nd Street
#1351 - Royal Oak, MI - 48068" with your name and email address with a written
description to be removed from our company mailing list.
Google.com Analytics
Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" may use Analytics tracking code to
support Display Advertising, and enable Google Analytics to collect data about your
traffic via the DoubleClick cookie in addition to data collected through the standard
Google Analytics implementation. Display Advertising lets us enable features in
Analytics that aren't available through standard implementations, like Remarketing with
Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick
Campaign Manager integration, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest
Reporting.
Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" may use Remarketing with Google
Analytics to advertise online:
This allows third-party vendors, including Google, to show your ads on sites across the
Internet. Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" and third-party vendors,
including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and
third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and
serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website.
Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" may implement Google Display
Network Impression Reporting or the DoubleClick Campaign Manager:
Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" and third-party vendors, including
Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party
cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how your ad impressions,
other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services that
are related to visits to your site.
Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" may implement Google Analytics
Demographics and Interest Reporting:
The data from Google's Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as
age, gender, and interests) with Google Analytics allows us to serve ads to you based on
this data.
Opting-out of Google Analytics' For The Web and Google Analytics for Display
Advertising:

Users can opt-out of Google Analytics' currently available opt-outs for the web at
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/
Using the Ads Settings, users can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising
and customize Google Display Network ads
athttps://www.google.com/settings/personalinfo
Retargeting Ad Campaigns and Persistent Identifiers:
Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" may utilize various types of
advertising that appear on our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" sites and
services including ads on third party sites and services. Our Company, "Ringold
Nutritional Systems, LLC" may utilize categories of information, including names and
email addresses, collected from users on our sites and services, as well as third party sites
and services, in connection with the ads that are served. This advertising may include, but
not limited to, contextual advertising, cookies, anonymous cookies, pixels, persistent
identifiers, geolocation information, email opt in, search engine terms, behavioral
advertising and/or retargeting advertising.
This type of advertising is a form of targeted advertising, to the specific individual who is
visiting the Web site. These advertisements appear on websites or other media, including
display ads, pop up ads and ads displayed in mobile browsers. Those advertisements are
selected and served by automated systems based on the interests relevant to the user from
the content displayed to the user, based on what the user is viewing.
Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" does not conduct inquiries into the
information collection practices of third parties that may collect information from users
that leave our Web site. Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" may share
customer information with third parties to process orders, for third party analytics and for
marketing and advertising purposes.
Responses to Email Inquiries: When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to our
Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC", the return email address is used to
answer the email inquiry we receive.
Voluntary Customer Surveys: We may periodically conduct both business and individual
customer surveys. We encourage our customers to participate in these surveys because
they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of products
and services we offer and how we provide them to you.
We may take the information we receive from individuals responding to our Customer
Surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other customers we may
have, to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age,
residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic

information). We then use the aggregated information to improve the quality of our
services to you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated, non-
personally identifying information may be shared with third parties.
Special Cases: It is our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC"'s policy to use or
share the personal information about Visitors or Members in ways described herein
without additional notice or means to opt out except as noted herein, or otherwise
prohibit such unrelated uses.
Also, we may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members, or information
regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, for any
reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: credit
agencies, collection agencies, merchant database agencies, law enforcement, or to satisfy
laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, the Child Online Privacy Act,
regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose
information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone
who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or Terms Of Service, or other user
policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect our Company, "Ringold
Nutritional Systems, LLC" and our Members.
Notice to California Residents – Your California Privacy Rights
Under California Law SB 27, California residents have the right to receive, once a
year, information about third parties with whom we have shared information about you
or your family for their marketing purposes during the previous calendar year, and a
description of the categories of personal information shared. To make such a request,
please send an email to Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC", to
optout@ringoldnutritional.com and please include the phrase "California Privacy
Request" in the subject line, the domain name of the Web site you are inquiring about,
along with your name, address and email address. We will respond to you within thirty
days of receiving such a request.
"Cookies" and How Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" Uses Them. A
"cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain
Web sites. Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" may use cookies to
collect, store, and sometimes track information for purposes stated herein as well as for
statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our
telecommunications networks.
Deleting Cookies: If you don't want our Company's, "Ringold Nutritional Systems,
LLC"'s cookies on your computer, to be used for the purposes stated herein, they are easy
to delete. Simply go to http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=2 for
instructions.
Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these
cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" Commitment to Children's Privacy:
Protecting children's privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with
the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws.
Therefore we restrict our Web site to persons eighteen years or older.
YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE.
IF YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED
TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE
RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THIS WEB SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED
BY THIS WEB SITE, FALLS WITHIN THE CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY
PROTECTION ACT (COPPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO.
Public Forums: Please remember that any information you may disclose in any Member
Directory, or other public areas of our Web sites or the Internet, becomes public
information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information
in these public areas.
Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC"'s Commitment to Data Security:
Services and Web sites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss,
misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort
to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that
our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this
information.
Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy: If you have any questions about
this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us through the
contact information provided on this Web site.
Revisions to This Policy: Our Company, "Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC" reserves
the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Terms Of Service agreement, and
our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, by updating this
posting. Your use of this site after such changes are implemented constitutes your
acknowledgement and acceptance of these changes. Please consult this privacy statement
prior to every use for any changes.
Last updated: January 23, 2015
         Copyright © 2003-2015 Attorney Bob Silber WebsiteLawForms.com and
                       Licensed To Ringold Nutritional Systems, LLC
